my summer is ripe the raspberries are
perfect for eating the calindala and
hollyhocks are in full bloom
it's beautiful and i cannot wait to make
something delicious with my harvest
[Music]
this week i realized something important
i've made so many videos about my
transition to a new life
shared the ups and downs and yet in my
heart
i still haven't moved on from my old
little cottage
still finding myself missing my old
routines and doings
everything that was so familiar
[Music]
everything is so new and different i
can't help but think back to my old life
and suddenly see things as so much
simpler
and yet they weren't not really
life is always beautiful and messy i
still felt complicated emotions back
then too it's funny how we look at the
past through rose-colored lenses
remembering what we want to not
necessarily what was
i was so happy at my old cottage but
also impatient to start a new life with
my partner if there is one truth my
little home and experiences have taught
me
is that your relationship with life is
one not unlike that of a friend or
partner
you must fall in love with it again and
again
find new ways to see joy and new
routines and habits to help you along
the way
[Music]
then
i think it's okay to have complicated
emotions
and resist change even when we want it
humans are funny that way
and like learning anything new it takes
time and dedication to reap the rewards
and we must allow ourselves to step into
the unknown from time to time if we feel
that the benefits are well worth the
risk
[Music]
my little home is now a memory and my
new life is here
in my present full of all the
necessities of shelter safety and love
and so there really isn't any reason to
hold on to the past
because all i ever needed was here all
along
[Music]
so i do have some exciting news and that
is that i am sitting
on a couch
we have been looking for a couch for a
very long time and if you
order a couch it can be quite difficult
to deliver it here because of the
long winding dirt roads and um we
finally did it we finally found one
so
we finally have somewhere to sit while
i've been going on this journey of
learning to
handle my emotions while i'm going
through such a drastic shift in life i
um did
notice that i have been dwelling
on my
former cottage quite a bit on social
media i notice it is quite popular to
showcase the transition to a new life be
that moving to a new country
starting life after marriage or just
moving into a new house i think of
course it is really exciting and fun to
share all that but i do think there's a
side to it that can be just so so
difficult you know as you may know i was
a military child my father was a naval
officer in the military for
my entire life
and so i moved around a lot and i moved
to new countries very often because we
were going to different places and
moving to different bases and there was
always this side of it that was so
exciting and wonderful and beautiful and
the side you want to photograph and
share but then there was this other side
of it was just it was really hard it was
an enormous shift in change everything
was different there were very few things
that felt familiar about your new
lifestyle and your new routine
and it could take
days if not weeks if not years
to get really used to a new pace of life
in a different place
and
thankfully i know that what got me
through all big changes in my life was
the people i love you know and
my family being there made anything
possible luke being with me on this
journey of starting a new life makes
everything possible and and makes it all
better and easier but it can still be
very challenging and of course in the
scheme of things it's so normal and not
really a big deal at the end of the day
everyone needs an adjustment period
but i thought it was just worth sharing
because i think it would be maybe useful
to talk about it's okay that things are
not perfect off the bat it's okay that
things are messy and rough sometimes as
you figure things out in a totally new
type of life and i have had so many
incredible moments of joy and so happy i
made this decision but also we've had
moments where luke and i have been wow
former lifestyle seems so much simpler
compared to this all these experiences
are bringing us closer so yes i just
thought it might be
really great to talk a little bit about
how we often romanticize the past when
we are facing challenges in the present
but yes in realization that i was
dwelling
more on the past than perhaps was
helpful to me i decided you know to try
to turn my energy a little more towards
the future and you may have seen that in
my last couple videos where i focused a
lot more on decorating and making my
house a home and making it feel like a
cozy space you know just ready to accept
all those incredible new memories oop
i sorry
sorry for the sudden shift and uh change
the uh mailman stopped by to deliver a
package and my dog went crazy and my cat
went crazy everyone went crazy so
we have finally brought peace back to
the household so i can add my last note
which was to say
thank you thank you so much for all your
kindness and support if you happen to
have ordered my book i'm going to go
more into detail with this in a future
video but after taking a look at the
final copy my editor and i realized that
there were just some formatting changes
that really had to be made and so to try
to ensure the you know kind of best
quality and best end result we just
decided to go ahead and push back the
release date to be able to make those
changes so if you order the book and
we're anticipating for it to come out
this month i sincerely sincerely
apologize for the delay it is still
coming out this year i do appreciate
your um understanding so thank you again
for the support in that way it is a
dream come true and i hope you all have
a wonderful week and you take care of
yourselves i'm sending you all my love
and i will see you very soon goodbye
you